Register of the Oleg Ivanovich Pantiukhov papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Russian scouting file, 1910-1989 and undated; Box 17-25 (Reel 24-39)
  - Printed matter
    - Poleznyiia sviedeniia, undated; Box/Folder 25: 4 (Reel 38)
    - Baden-Powell, Robert. Iunyi razviedchik, 1910(?); Box/Folder 25: 5 (Reel 38)
    - Bud' gotov: pamiatka o russkikh skautakh, 1929; Box/Folder 25: 6 (Reel 39)
    - Zelenyi shum: skautskii nomer, 1929 May; Box/Folder 25: 7 (Reel 39)
    - Rossiiskoe razvedchestvo, 1948; Box/Folder 25: 8 (Reel 39)
    - Russian Scout News, #1 (1958), #5 (1959), Box/Folder 25: 9 (Reel 39)
    - U kostra: listok vneshkol'nogo vospitaniia, 1959; Box/Folder 25: 10 (Reel 39)
    - Rossiiskoe razdedchestvo (ego tseli i zadachi), 1963; Box/Folder 25: 11 (Reel 39)
  - Miscellany, undated; Box/Folder 25: 12 (Reel 39)
- Subject file, 1927-1989 and undated; Box/Folder 26: (Reel 39)
  Banknotes, clippings, correspondence, lists, reports, writings and other matter arranged alphabetically by subject heading and chronologically therein
  - Anticommunism, 1934-1989.; Box/Folder 26: 1 (Reel 39)
    See also Oversize file/Den' neprimirimosti
  - Den' russkoi kul'tury, 1927-1932 and undated.; Box/Folder 26: 2 (Reel 39)
    See also Oversize file/Subject file/Den' russkoi kul'tury
  - Dzhuliani, Aleksandr Ivanovich, 1928-1939(?).; Box/Folder 26: 3 (Reel 39)
    Includes letters and cars to him from P. Karsakov and E. Miller (?)
  - Natsional'naia organizatsiia vitiazei, 1934-1960; Box/Folder 26: 4 (Reel 39)
  - Romanov family, 1961-1981 and undated; Box/Folder 26: 5 (Reel 39)
  - Russia. Armiia, 1928-1973
    - Gvardeiskoe ob"edinenie, 1950-1973 and undated; Box/Folder 26: 6 (Reel 39)
    - Leib-gvardii 1-yi Strelkovyi Ego Velichestva polk, 1928-1973 and undated.; Box/Folder 26: 7 (Reel 39)
      Includes materials related to the campaigns of the regiment in the World War, 1914-1918, as well as activities of its veteran's society abroad
  - Russia. Gosudarstvennyi bank, currency (banknotes), Undated; Box/Folder 26: 8 (Reel 39)
  - Russia (Territory under White Armies, 1918-1920)., Box/Folder 26: 9 (Reel 39)
    Excerpts of undated typescript by unknown author, entitled "Vostochnyi front," and detailing Civil War in Siberia, 1918-1919
  - Russians, 1929 and undated
    - Miami, Florida, undated, Box/Folder 26: 10 (Reel 39)
    - Nice, France, 1929 and undated; Box/Folder 26: 11 (Reel 39)
  - Russkii obshchevoinskii soiuz, 1934-1974.; Box/Folder 26: 12 (Reel 39)
  - Soiuz georgievskikh kavalerov, 1960-1969; Box/Folder 26: 13 (Reel 39)
    A portion of this material deals with the relationship between ROVS and the scouting movement; includes correspondence between O. I. Pantiukhov and various figures involved in negotiations with ROVS
  - Young Communist League of Great Britain, 1927; Box/Folder 26: 14 (Reel 39)
  - Miscellany, 1932-1963 and undated; Box/Folder 26: 15 (Reel 39)
    Includes photocopies of interview and statements by William Rust and Robert Baden-Powell
- Oversize file, 1920-1986 and undated; Box/Folder 27: (Reel 39)
  Clippings, subject file and writings, mainly on Russian scouting, arranged alphabetically by physical form and chronologically therein
  - Clippings, 1920-1986 and undated
    - Russian Scouts, 1920-1986; Box/Folder 27: 1 (Reel 39)
    - Miscellany, undated, Box/Folder 27: 2 (Reel 39)
  - Subject file
    - Den' neprimirimosti, 1934; Box/Folder 27: 3 (Reel 39)
    - Den' russkoi kul'tury, 1930-1931 and undated.; Box/Folder 27: 4 (Reel 39)
  - Writings on Russian scouting, 1923-1924.; Box/Folder 27: 5 (Reel 39)
    Issuance